Phone: (+98)9371434110 Tehran , Iran farzaadshojaei@gmail.com

Farzad Shojaei

Test Engineer

github.com/FarzaadShojaei linkedin.com/in/farzad-shojaei

SUMMERY

Each project has been a step toward excellence, showing that with the right attitude. With a background in both the technical and teamwork aspects of software projects with More than 100 thousands active users, Trying to Establish the Software Development Life Cycle (SDLC), Software Testing Life Cycle (STLC), and ISTQB standards with a close working relationship maintained with technical teams. Fostering a culture of open communication and mutual respect, This involved facilitating solution-oriented discussions with product visions.

SKILLS

• Cypress •JavaScript •Git •Postman •CI/CD •K6 •Jira

WORK EXPERIENCE

Test Engineer / Mofid Securities Tehran, Iran

January 2023 — Present

Mofid Securities is Iran's largest full-service stock brokerage firm leading private investment advisory with more that 10 million active Users.

- Enhanced the working flow by identifying the pain points and bottlenecks of the team through meetings with tech leads and Product Owners. leading to 40% rise in positive feedbacks.
- Created an exclusive RTM and a Testing Checklist to increase Test coverage of various sections of the application in **Jira** based on specific needs of team. resulting to **50% reduce** in releasing android versions based on OKR Reports.
- Formed Automation Testing and API Testing Flows From Scratch using **Cypress** and **Postman Tests** Based On the Testing Checklist. leading to a **50% save** in Acceptance testing time.
- Establishing CI/CD process, in collaboration with the Infrastructure team in **Gitlab CI**,leading to the formation of versioning workflows for both application and website.

Software Tester / Panco.app

June 2022 — December 2022

Tehran,Iran

Pance.app The First Social Networking Platform in Iran with more than **100 thousand** active users per day, Focused on playing **mobile games** and Communicating alongside each other

- Designed over 200 test cases and scenarios considering The testing checklist for **manual testing**. resulted in finding several critical crashes in games
- Monitored Continuously the impact of the changes through metrics and feedback.

EDUCATION

Bachelor Of Computer Engineering, *University of Science and Culture*

September 2019 - June 2023

LANGUAGES

English: Bilingual French: Intermediate